Mohd Ariz Siddiqui



SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Kattankulathur, Tamil Nadu, India — IN 603203

M +91 8860896000

E <u>arizsiddiqui@hotmail.com</u>
W <u>www.arizsiddiqui.tech</u>

L <u>arizsiddiqui</u>

B <u>arizsiddiqui.medium.com</u>

Profile

I am a passionate final year computer science and engineering student with hands on experience in coding and software development. A quick learner with strong communication and inter-personal skills, I have successfully contributed to technical team success in projects with hard-work and attention-to-details. Additionally, cleared foundational level and now pursuing Diploma level skills in programming & data science from IIT Madras.

Experience

NVIDIA Corporation - 2021 - 2022 (Intern)

Worked as an ML Intern at NVIDIA Corporation for 6 months, working on multiple research projects using proprietary SDKs like DeepStream, Clara, Riva and toolkits like NeMo. Published 3 blogs at Medium.com based on my research. Additionally, served as a Teaching Assistant for multiple workshops hosted by NVIDIA as part of the Deep Learning Institute (DLI).

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassadors SRM – 2019 – 2021 (ML Developer)

Completed multiple projects under the banner of the technical team of the club, including a NLP based browser extension, a CLI for keeping API and OAuth Tokens safe and a webinar on the basics of Python. Also, organised a hackathon, Resonate, with 500+ attendees.

Aaruush – 2019—2022 (Volunteer, Committee Member, Committee Head)

Helped organise one of the largest techno-management fests in South India, playing a role in guest invitation and itinerary management. Personally tended to high-profile guests and successfully managed crisis situations.

Nirmal Bhartia School - 2018 - 2019 (Head Boy)

Served as the head of the student council of the school, helping implement regulations that improved the school life of the students.

Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Madras, Tamil Nadu

Pursuing B.Sc. in Programming and Data Science (Diploma Level)

SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Kattankulathur, Tamil Nadu Pursuing B.Tech. Computer Science and Engineering (Final Year)

Technical Skills

Python, C, C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Swift, MySQL, Oracle, Git, Bash/Zsh, awk, sed, Docker, Flask, OpenCV, TensorFlow, Numpy, Pandas, Bootstrap, Scikit-learn, Scipy, Keras.

Soft Skills

Communication, Attention to detail, Quick learner, Delivers under pressure, Team worker.